[
 {
   "question": "taberna",
   "answer": "bar"
 },
 {
   "question": "komuna",
   "answer": "bathroom"
 },
 {
   "question": "hondartza",
   "answer": "beach"
 },
 {
   "question": "logela",
   "answer": "bedroom"
 },
 {
   "question": "odola",
   "answer": "blood"
 },
 {
   "question": "mutil",
   "answer": "boy"
 },
 {
   "question": "kafetegia",
   "answer": "cafe"
 },
 {
   "question": "auto",
   "answer": "car"
 },
 {
   "question": "arotza",
   "answer": "carpenter"
 },
 {
   "question": "gaztaina",
   "answer": "chestnut"
 },
 {
   "question": "zinema",
   "answer": "cinema"
 },
 {
   "question": "hiria",
   "answer": "city"
 },
 {
   "question": "hodei",
   "answer": "cloud"
 },
 {
   "question": "ordenagailu",
   "answer": "computer"
 },
 {
   "question": "sendagilea",
   "answer": "doctor"
 },
 {
   "question": "ate",
   "answer": "door"
 },
 {
   "question": "ingeniaria",
   "answer": "engineer"
 },
 {
   "question": "enpresaburua",
   "answer": "entrepreneur"
 },
 {
   "question": "baserria",
   "answer": "farm"
 },
 {
   "question": "arrantzalea",
   "answer": "fisherman"
 },
 {
   "question": "futbolaria",
   "answer": "footballer"
 },
 {
   "question": "lagun",
   "answer": "friend"
 },
 {
   "question": "lorategi",
   "answer": "garden"
 },
 {
   "question": "neska",
   "answer": "girl"
 },
 {
   "question": "edalontzi",
   "answer": "glass"
 },
 {
   "question": "etxea",
   "answer": "house"
 },
 {
   "question": "etxekoandrea",
   "answer": "housewife"
 },
 {
   "question": "giltza",
   "answer": "key"
 },
 {
   "question": "sukaldea",
   "answer": "kitchen"
 },
 {
   "question": "egongela",
   "answer": "living room"
 },
 {
   "question": "gizon",
   "answer": "man"
 },
 {
   "question": "alkatea",
   "answer": "mayor"
 },
 {
   "question": "mendi",
   "answer": "mountain"
 },
 {
   "question": "auzoa",
   "answer": "neighborhood"
 },
 {
   "question": "galtza",
   "answer": "pants"
 },
 {
   "question": "gurasoa",
   "answer": "parent"
 },
 {
   "question": "iturgina",
   "answer": "plumber"
 },
 {
   "question": "politikaria",
   "answer": "politician"
 },
 {
   "question": "postaria",
   "answer": "postman"
 },
 {
   "question": "probintzia",
   "answer": "province"
 },
 {
   "question": "eskualdea",
   "answer": "region"
 },
 {
   "question": "eskola",
   "answer": "school"
 },
 {
   "question": "itsasoa",
   "answer": "sea"
 },
 {
   "question": "alkandora",
   "answer": "shirt"
 },
 {
   "question": "oinetako/zapata",
   "answer": "shoe"
 },
 {
   "question": "zerua",
   "answer": "sky"
 },
 {
   "question": "denda",
   "answer": "store"
 },
 {
   "question": "kalea",
   "answer": "street"
 },
 {
   "question": "eguzkia",
   "answer": "sun"
 },
 {
   "question": "jertsea",
   "answer": "sweater"
 },
 {
   "question": "mahai",
   "answer": "table"
 },
 {
   "question": "irakaslea",
   "answer": "teacher"
 },
 {
   "question": "herria",
   "answer": "town"
 },
 {
   "question": "aterki",
   "answer": "umbrella"
 },
 {
   "question": "herrixka",
   "answer": "village"
 },
 {
   "question": "bide",
   "answer": "way"
 },
 {
   "question": "gurpil",
   "answer": "wheel"
 },
 {
   "question": "emakume",
   "answer": "woman"
 },
 {
   "question": "lantokia",
   "answer": "workplace"
 }
]